bidray.com 2010-03-11

# Penny Auctions - Bidray | Bid & Win Penny Auctions!

Bidray Ltd.

Suite 404 324 Regent Street  
London  
United Kingdom  
W1B 3HH  
Company No.06719888

1\. General

Your data is collected and processed by us exclusively according to statutory regulations.  
You may use Bidray at any time without registering. When you visit our website, data is saved on our servers in an anonymous format, as is the website that you visit us from, the websites that you proceed to from our site, and your IP address.  
As this is being done, no personal data is associated with you. However, we do need some personal information from you so that you can actively participate in Bidray.  
We would therefore like to request that you agree to the collection and storage of some of your data.  
You can revoke your consent any time by closing your account with us.   
Once you have register with Bidray, you are asked to choose a Bidray user name together with a password, which then allows you to take advantage of all of the Bidray services.

2\. Data Collection

"Personal data" is the information needed to identify you, for example your name, address, date of birth, e-mail address, mobile phone number, etc. With your consent, personal data are recorded and processed by Bidray, in particular: 

-When you register with "My Bidray"  
-When you purchase bids  
-When you win an auction  
-When you securely login

Credit card data will never be stored or handled by us. Instead, all credit card transactions are securely handled by the payment processor DalPay.  
"Usage data" are personal data that identify the user, as well as information on the Bidray services the user utilizes, for example your Bidray user name together with the associated password and your IP address when you purchase bids, login to the site or win an auction.  
We collect these data only to make it possible for you to use Bidray.

3\. Use of the Data

Personal data such as name, address, etc. are used to process item shipment after an auction is won. We ask for your e-mail address so that we can stay in contact with you by e-mail.   
We need your account data to process payment transactions that you are involved with. We also use your personal data to communicate with you regarding orders, to process auctions, marketing retentions and to process other transactions.  
Similarly, we use your data in order to inform you of marketing promotions or to enable third parties authorized by us to perform technical, logistical, or other services.  
All data is stored securely on our servers.

4\. Newsletter

When you register with Bidray, you agree to be signed up with our newsletter. You may at anytime unsubscribe from the newsletter by going to this page  
or clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter emails.

5\. Forwarding Personal Data to Third Parties

Your personal information may be passed on to third parties only if this is necessary to process a payment transaction or a business transaction with our partners.  
Essentially these are respectable businesses that strictly comply with applicable data protection regulations.  
Bidray will not release any personal information on you or forward this to third parties insofar as you have not given your express consent to do so, or unless we are required to do so by law. When you use Bidray and bid by SMS, you consent to have your phone number provided to Bidray by the phone company so that you can be notified in the case that you win an auction or if you are outbid by another user.  
We may use your phone number to contact you later on with special offers or other information in regard with Bidray.  
By trying out our free SMS text message bidding service, you agree to be signed up with our "Special Offers & News" newsletter for SMS. You may at any time unsubscribe from this service by simply replying with the text "FINISH" to our number, or by logging in to your Bidray account and changing your SMS newsletter settings.  
In other situations, personal data will be passed on only to the extent that we are required to do so by law. For example, personal data is passed on to prosecutorial authorities.

7\. Viewing/Changing Personal Data

You can view the information in your Bidray account at any time and update it as necessary using your Bidray user name and your Bidray password.   
Your mobile phone number for activating your account can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service.   
Once we are informed, we will adjust incorrect data accordingly.  
We will notify you upon request at any time as to whether and what personal data in respect to your identity or your pseudonym has been stored.

8\. Revoking Consent/Deleting Your Account

You can revoke your consent to the storage and processing of your personal data here at any time, effective immediately.   
You can delete or deactivate your Bidray account at any time. When you delete your membership, your personal data is removed from our database unless we are required to save the data.   
As a rule it takes two to three weeks until your information is completely removed from all records. If you choose to close your account, all remaining bids will be destroyed.

9\. The Use of Cookies at our Website

Bidray uses so-called "cookies", which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service.  
The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example by keeping track of your bids placed, auctions, etc.  
It is necessary to accept cookies in order to use our service properly.   
We would like to point out that turning off these settings may result in limited functionality.

10\. Security Measures

The information in your Bidray account and in your Bidray profile is password protected, so that only you have access to this personal information.   
Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else.   
Bidray will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request.   
Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave the Bidray site; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations.  
At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information.   
We assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.

11\. Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam

Bidray assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms and Conditions.  
We will not sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web crawlers" or "web spiders" to the best of our ability.  
If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

12\. Data Protection Guidelines Changes

We reserve the right to change this document at any time, without prior notification.
